Dominic Chavarria

Frontend Web Developer

9085 Mast Blvd #130 Lakeside, CA, 92040 savagedialects@gmail.com || 7205867511 Linkedin: www.linkedin.com/in/viqqridtc Github: https://github.com/notagainnn

Summary

I am an analytical web developer with 8 years of team leadership experience. I pride myself in being highly motivated and a proficient problem solver with a keen eye for detail. I have successfully lead multiple teams to yield better results in less time with an attention to detail.

Experience

Addon Writer

2005- Present

- Would write and edit LUA code to create game-play addons for games such as World of Warcraft.
- · Customized previous build addons to meet user's needs.

Chef

Zafferano Catering LLC | April 2021- October 2021

- Lead diverse teams of up to 7 chefs to meet deadlines for large orders.
- Managed overall quality of all stations while troubleshooting problems in the moment.

Pastry Chef

Pappalecco | October 2021- Present

- Manages large orders of items to multiple locations throughout the city.
- Helps update items to customers requests and changing trends.

Education

Web Development General Assembly | January 2022- March 2022 Diploma Lawrence Free State HS, Lawrence, KS | 2005 - 2009

Key Skills

- JavaScript
- Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)
- HTML
- Bootstrap
- git

Certifications

• FEWD at General Assembly | April 2022

Accomplishments

- Collaborated with other Chefs to achieve a James Beard award at Mercantile Dining & Provision in Denver, Colorado.
- Managed ordering, scheduling and menu design at a startup restaurant.
- Graduated GA's FEWD course ahead of my class and assisted the instructors with helping other students.